A Guide to the Secretary of the Commonwealth, Executive Journals 1992
Library of Virginia
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 June 12, Campbell, Winston Dale (Box 6, Folder 49)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 June 12, Nester, Harold Dewayne (Box 6, Folder 50)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 June 12, Walters, Harry Lloyd (Box 6, Folder 51)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 June 12, Smith, Ricky Duane (Box 6, Folder 52)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 June 12, Green, Richard Cecil (Box 6, Folder 53)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 June 12, Johnson, Roger Lee (Box 6, Folder 54)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 June 12, Stephenson, Michael Keith (Box 6, Folder 55)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 June 12, McDaniel, Lloyd Eugene (Box 6, Folder 56)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 June 12, Talbot, Tracy Eugene (Box 6, Folder 57)
- RESTRICTED: List of Contents, 1992 July-August (Box 7, Folder 1)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 July 7, Thompson, Markle Carlton (Box 7, Folder 2)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 July 8, Eason, Janet Moore (Box 7, Folder 3)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 July 10, Braithwaite, Steven Allen (Box 7, Folder 4)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 July 10, Laury, Kevin Jerome (Box 7, Folder 5)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 July 10, Lauray, Wayne Amiel (Box 7, Folder 6)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 July 20, Hale, Howard Dewayne, Jr. (Box 7, Folder 7)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 July 23, Wells, Gordon Tony Lee (Box 7, Folder 8)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 July 27, Music, Johnny (Box 7, Folder 9)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 6, Wirth, Beth Ann (Box 7, Folder 10)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 6, Prow, Kathryn M. (Box 7, Folder 11)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 6, Johnson, Jacqueline (Box 7, Folder 12)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 6, Hopson, Ronald E. (Box 7, Folder 13)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 6, McCauley, Harold Timothy (Box 7, Folder 14)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 8, Colbert, John, Jr. (Box 7, Folder 15)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 6, Benetatos, Henry Charles (Box 7, Folder 16)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 6, Santiago, Angel Manuel (Box 7, Folder 17)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 6, Cope, Benny Joe, Jr. (Box 7, Folder 18)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 6, Martin, Kenneth N. (Box 7, Folder 19)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 8, Ford, James Eddie (Box 7, Folder 20)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 8, Kidd, Lawrence Dale (Box 7, Folder 21)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 8, Blankenship, Clark Cletus, II (Box 7, Folder 22)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 8, Hollins, Glenn Eddie (Box 7, Folder 23)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 8, Clayton, Jasper Moston (Box 7, Folder 24)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 8, Glover, Michelle A. (Box 7, Folder 25)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 8, Ricky McCoy Taylor AKA Ricky Chavis (Box 7, Folder 26)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 20, Johnson, Charles Wendell (Box 7, Folder 27)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 24, Caulder, Burnice Cleveland (Box 7, Folder 28)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 8, David Chambers AKA Kevin Storme (Box 7, Folder 29)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 July 7, Edwards, Mary Lee (Box 7, Folder 30)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 August 7, Brady, Terry Franklin (Box 7, Folder 31)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 August 13, Cann, Kimberly Michelle (Box 7, Folder 32)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 August 14, Spangler, Raymond (Box 7, Folder 33)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 August 19, Ratterree, Donald Dean (Box 7, Folder 34)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 August 20, Marlon Poindexter AKA Marion Poindexter AKA Marlon D. Poindexter (Box 7, Folder 35)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 August 21, John Jerry Scharf AKA Jerry Scharf (Box 7, Folder 36)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 August 21, Lemonte Everett Christopher Allen AKA Chris Allen (Box 7, Folder 37)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 August 27, Davenport, Tonia Lee (Box 7, Folder 38)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 August 27, McCoy, Eugene C. (Box 7, Folder 39)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 August 27, Robinson, David John (Box 7, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 August 27, White, Gregory Lynn (Box 7, Folder 41)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 August 31, Larry Roye AKA Lawrence Robert Roye (Box 7, Folder 42)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 3, Holmes, Jerome Darnell (Box 7, Folder 43)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 3, Kirk A. Abbott AKA Rory Alvaranga (Box 7, Folder 44)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 3, Cook, Celeste Patrick (Box 7, Folder 45)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 3, Jefferson, Ronald (Box 7, Folder 46)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 5, Younger, James Michael (Box 7, Folder 47)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 5, Paolozzi, Frank Thomas (Box 7, Folder 48)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 14, Painter, Vivian E. (Box 7, Folder 49)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 17, Hooper, Maurice (Box 7, Folder 50)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 17, Hinton, Francis, Alvin (Box 7, Folder 51)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 17, Mills, Richard Dean (Box 7, Folder 52)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 17, Busch, Keith Alan (Box 7, Folder 53)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 17, Loggins, Jacqueline M. (Box 7, Folder 54)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 17, Paul, Charles Joseph (Box 7, Folder 55)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 17, Bernardo, Michael A. (Box 7, Folder 56)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 17, Hardy, Amanda (Box 7, Folder 57)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 17, Williams, Donnie Ray (Box 7, Folder 58)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 17, Blankenship, Terry Lynn (Box 7, Folder 59)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 25, Broger, Timothy E. (Box 7, Folder 60)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 25, Horton, Andrew Jackson (Box 7, Folder 61)
- RESTRICTED: List of Contents, 1992 August-November (Box 8, Folder 1)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 25, Sherry R. Bell AKA Sherry Hensberger (Box 8, Folder 2)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 25, Favor, Roy (Box 8, Folder 3)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 25, Knott, Robert Edward (Box 8, Folder 4)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 25, Mayo, Edward S. (Box 8, Folder 5)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 25, Newsome, Willard (Box 8, Folder 6)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 26, Valencia, Munoz Guillermo (Box 8, Folder 7)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 26, Hill, Jerri Halfen (Box 8, Folder 8)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 31, Edwards, Elizabeth Ann (Box 8, Folder 9)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 31, Allen, William G. (Box 8, Folder 10)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 31, Bazemore, Ronald (Box 8, Folder 11)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 31, Robinson, Mamie Arlene (Box 8, Folder 12)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 August 31, Sendaj, Theresa Lynn (Box 8, Folder 13)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 September 8, Leite, Michael John (Box 8, Folder 14)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 September 10, Rivera, Jose Luis (Box 8, Folder 15)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 September 14, Ellison, Perry Baxter (Box 8, Folder 16)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 September 14, Turnbull, Ludence Alford (Box 8, Folder 17)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 September 16, Thomas Lee AKA Thomas Kahaloa Lee (Box 8, Folder 18)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 September 21, Sadler, Karl E. (Box 8, Folder 19)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 September 21, Dean, David Allen (Box 8, Folder 20)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 September 28, Katheryne Reese Steele AKA Katheryn Reese Steele AKA Kathryn Reese Steele (Box 8, Folder 21)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 September 29, Martin, Brian Michael (Box 8, Folder 22)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 5, Anthony Michael Eagle AKA Julian T. McCartney (Box 8, Folder 23)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 5, Forth, Brian Scott (Box 8, Folder 24)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 5, Shepperson, Michael V. (Box 8, Folder 25)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 9, Todd Christopher Stewart AKA Todd Christopher Keller (Box 8, Folder 26)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 9, Testa, Charles (Box 8, Folder 27)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 9, Abner, Willie J. (Box 8, Folder 28)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 21, Sharon Cobb AKA Sharon Mills (Box 8, Folder 29)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 21, Perkins, Randall K. (Box 8, Folder 30)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 21, Campbell, John E. (Box 8, Folder 31)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 21, Cherrington, Lillian Mae (Box 8, Folder 32)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 21, Edgar J. Skaggs AKA Ronald Hawkins (Box 8, Folder 33)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 23, Ray, Anthony Eugene (Box 8, Folder 34)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 26, Kendrick Sherrod Jones AKA Kendrick Sherraud Jones (Box 8, Folder 35)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 26, Holliday, David Wilbur (Box 8, Folder 36)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 26, Bolesta, Dale Chester (Box 8, Folder 37)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 26, Presley, Nathan C. (Box 8, Folder 38)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 26, Patterson, Darren Michael (Box 8, Folder 39)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 21, Smith, Stephen P. (Box 8, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 30, Phuc Huu Luc AKA Phuc H. Luc (Box 8, Folder 41)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 30, Ifueko Esemude AKA Doug Monts (Box 8, Folder 42)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 30, Battle, Ricky Lavelle (Box 8, Folder 43)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 30, Stevens, Malissa Diane (Box 8, Folder 44)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 November 2, Penny C. Bingaman AKA Penny Bingaman (Box 8, Folder 45)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 November 2, James C. Collins AKA James J. Collins (Box 8, Folder 46)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 November 2, Johnny Carl Stephens AKA Shawn Paul Hoffman (Box 8, Folder 47)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 November 2, Alvester Christian AKA Bummy (Box 8, Folder 48)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 November 4, Joseph Harver AKA Joseph Wilbur Harver (Box 8, Folder 49)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 November 4, Toney Alexander Minor AKA Anthoney Darnell Williams (Box 8, Folder 50)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 November 6, Larry E. Stokes AKA Larry Edgar Stokes (Box 8, Folder 51)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 November 6, Friend, Gwenevere G. (Box 8, Folder 52)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 November 16, Richard B. Anderson AKA Richard Benjamin Anderson (Box 8, Folder 53)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 November 19, Ein, Robert John (Box 8, Folder 54)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 November 24, Jones, James Allen (Box 8, Folder 55)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 November 30, LeMasters, Ronald Eugene (Box 8, Folder 56)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 November 30, Zimmerman, Glen (Box 8, Folder 57)
- RESTRICTED: List of Contents, 1992 November-December (Box 9, Folder 1)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 November 13, Miller, John Karl (Box 9, Folder 2)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 November 13, Ejjam, Ali Widad (Box 9, Folder 3)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 November 13, Robert M. McQueen AKA Robert Matthew McQueen (Box 9, Folder 4)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 November 13, William Clark Terry AKA William C. Terry AKA Larry L. Wilson (Box 9, Folder 5)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 November 23, Hatch, Kevin (Box 9, Folder 6)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 November 23, Taylor, Edward Joseph (Box 9, Folder 7)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 November 23, Hash, John Christopher (Box 9, Folder 8)
- RESTRICTED: Unconditional Pardon, Medical Furlough, 1992 November 24, Velasquez, Alex Manuel (Box 9, Folder 9)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 3, Alfred Kevin Scott (Box 9, Folder 10)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 3, Weatherford, Thomas G. (Box 9, Folder 11)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 3, Ivey, Johnnie Edward (Box 9, Folder 12)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 4, Johnny Connors AKA Johnny Conner AKA Johnny S. Conner (Box 9, Folder 13)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 9, Gholson, Larry Maurice (Box 9, Folder 14)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 9, Ning, Samuel (Box 9, Folder 15)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 9, Avan Armstrong AKA Tyrone Smith AKA Geroge Sidney Armstrong (Box 9, Folder 16)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 9, Boykins, George (Box 9, Folder 17)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 9, Triplett, Michael Ross (Box 9, Folder 18)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 9, Lewis, Lionel (Box 9, Folder 19)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 16, Temen, Jeremy (Box 9, Folder 20)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 28, Ted Moore AKA Ted Broadus Moore AKA Theodore Moore (Box 9, Folder 21)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 30, Forbus, Michael Edward (Box 9, Folder 22)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 December 7, Sharon Lee Sandross AKA Sharon Lee Sandross Bennett (Box 9, Folder 23)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 December 7, Beckelman, Carroll Albert (Box 9, Folder 24)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 December 7, Feliciano, George (Box 9, Folder 25)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 December 7, Baker, June Lazoe (Box 9, Folder 26)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 December 7, Saliba, Henry A. (Box 9, Folder 27)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 December 7, Simmons, Anthony Eugene (Box 9, Folder 28)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 October 30, Mendez, Margaret (Box 9, Folder 29)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 December 7, Porsirio Mendez (Pilo) Deltora AKA Detoro (Box 9, Folder 30)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 December 21, O'Brien, Jack Gordon (Box 9, Folder 31)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 December 21, Browning, Anna D. (Box 9, Folder 32)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 December 21, Sizer, Wyche Larry (Box 9, Folder 33)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 December 21, Walker, Paul Curtis (Box 9, Folder 34)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 December 21, William David Crites AKA William David Crites, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 35)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 December 21, Trinh, The Minh (Box 9, Folder 36)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 December 21, Loner, James Nathaniel (Box 9, Folder 37)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 December 21, Patrick, Ronnie Gayle (Box 9, Folder 38)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 December 21, Sames, Richard Henry, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 39)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 December 21, Price, Michael Sean (Box 9, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 December 21, Zagade, Zahidali Abdul Sattar (Box 9, Folder 41)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 23, Branch, Joseph Charles (Box 9, Folder 42)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 28, Jenkins, Jeffrey Allan (Box 9, Folder 43)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 28, Lappel, Robert Richard (Box 9, Folder 44)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 28, Sherman D. Manning AKA Sherman Diahrick Manning (Box 9, Folder 45)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 December 30, Shaver, Claude Thomas (Box 9, Folder 46)